The Eminence in Shadow
Since the incident at the Bushin Festival,
the Cult of Diablos in the Midgar Kingdom
has shown no signs of conspicuous activity.
The smaller sects were at a standstill,
as well as the Fenrir sect due to the confusion
amidst their restructuring.
It is all going exactly
as you've planned, My Lord.
Now we can set our sights forward and focus our main efforts
on the situation in the Oriana Kingdom.
But there is a troubling bit of news.
There has been a recent acceleration
in the flow of funds going into the Lawless City.
Funds?
That region doesn't belong to any nation.
It's a giant slum where the evil,
wealth, and power of the world converge.
Any tensions that occur in that region could have
an immeasurable effect on the rest of society.
Although we would like to focus
all our efforts on accomplishing our plan,
I suggest we dispatch reinforcements to—
I smell it.
The Lawless City reeks of blood.
A storm is brewing...
A storm of blood.
The moon...
It's unusually...
Crimson.
In fact, it looks just like the legendary...
Red Moon.
The tragedy of a thousand years ago...
In that case, the Lawless City will...
No, if nothing is done, all surrounding nations
will be subjected to catastrophic damage.
Silence, all of you.
If that is an omen of the Red Moon,
we cannot merely sit here
and gaze idly at the sky.
We Seven Shades will—
No.
Let me handle the money—
I mean, this matter.
No! Do you intend
to go there alone, My Lord?
You object?
We understand that would be
the surest method, however...
Should the unthinkable happen
to you, we would...
Fear not.
The moon has turned red, that is all.
Is it not?
No more than a moon turned red...
Faced with you, even the legendary Red Moon
is stripped of its dignity.
Do you not find the moon
to be just as beautiful when red?
It is because we have you, My Lord, that we, too,
are able to appreciate its radiance.
We wish you the best of luck in battle.
At first, it was nothing more
than an ordinary moon,
Your will be done in all things, My Lord.
practically unchanged,
but with just a hint of red.
I'll analyze dragon tears or something
while I await your return.
And so no one knew that it was a portent,
a harbinger, of the revival of the Blood Queen.
No one, save for the Great Shadow!
Get these girls involved,
and the legendary Red Moon comes to life
in the blink of an eye.
Seriously, their ad-libbing skills
are totally worthy of an Academy Award.
It's just a kinda reddish moon, no biggie.
m -418.19 19.34 b -418.19 17.61 -418.28 15.89 -418.47 14.2 -410.75 14.31 -405.77 14.38 -403.56 14.38 -401.34 14.38 -396.38 14.31 -388.64 14.2 -388.91 16.55 -389.05 18.27 -389.05 19.34 l -389.45 19.34 b -393.72 18.27 -397.36 17.69 -400.36 17.61 -400.55 19.61 -400.64 22.7 -400.64 26.89 l -400.64 42.77 b -400.64 47.95 -400.36 51.83 -399.78 54.36 l -399.78 54.77 -407.34 54.77 -407.34 54.36 b -406.84 51.86 -406.59 48.08 -406.59 43 l -406.59 27.13 b -406.59 22.78 -406.69 19.61 -406.88 17.61 -409.8 17.69 -413.44 18.27 -417.78 19.34 l -418.19 19.34 m -378.7 23.31 l -378.7 31.22 b -377.25 30.11 -376.13 29.28 -375.33 28.75 -374.55 28.2 -373.53 27.67 -372.28 27.16 -371.03 26.64 -369.84 26.38 -368.73 26.38 -365.88 26.38 -363.69 27.27 -362.14 29.03 -360.61 30.8 -359.84 33.34 -359.84 36.64 l -359.84 44.95 b -359.84 48.61 -359.27 51.75 -358.11 54.36 l -358.11 54.77 -366.25 54.77 -366.25 54.36 b -365.59 52.44 -365.27 49.88 -365.27 46.69 l -365.27 37.86 b -365.27 35.63 -365.59 33.95 -366.28 32.81 -366.95 31.67 -368.34 31.11 -370.48 31.11 -372.63 31.11 -375.3 32.09 -378.53 34.05 l -378.53 44.95 b -378.53 48.69 -377.98 51.83 -376.86 54.36 l -376.86 54.77 -384.94 54.77 -384.94 54.36 b -384.28 52.44 -383.95 49.88 -383.95 46.69 l -383.95 20.89 b -383.95 17.81 -384.84 15.44 -386.61 13.73 l -386.61 13.05 -378.88 11.66 -378.53 12.23 b -378.66 13.36 -378.7 17.05 -378.7 23.31 l -378.7 23.31 m -339.53 55.41 b -343.56 55.41 -346.72 54.16 -349 51.66 -351.27 49.16 -352.41 45.86 -352.41 41.75 -352.41 37.66 -351.13 34.08 -348.59 31 -346.05 27.92 -342.89 26.38 -339.13 26.38 -332.23 26.38 -328.8 30.63 -328.8 39.13 l -330.94 41.2 -346.28 41.2 b -346.28 44.44 -345.59 46.86 -344.2 48.48 -342.81 50.09 -340.95 50.91 -338.61 50.91 -337.69 50.91 -336.38 50.63 -334.69 50.06 -332.98 49.5 -331.48 48.84 -330.19 48.08 l -328.73 50.27 b -329.47 51 -331.06 52.03 -333.5 53.38 -335.94 54.73 -337.95 55.41 -339.53 55.41 l -339.53 55.41 m -340.17 29.27 b -341.78 29.27 -343.03 29.63 -343.92 30.36 -344.64 31.36 -345.22 32.63 -345.64 34.17 -346.06 35.7 -346.28 37.05 -346.28 38.2 l -334.45 37.75 b -334.45 32.09 -336.36 29.27 -340.17 29.27 l -340.17 29.27 m -307.2 54.77 l -307.2 54.36 b -306.63 52.13 -306.34 48.23 -306.34 42.66 l -306.34 26.48 b -306.34 20.92 -306.63 17.02 -307.2 14.78 l -307.2 14.38 -299.53 14.38 -299.53 14.78 b -299.77 15.7 -299.97 17.56 -300.14 20.34 -300.31 23.14 -300.39 25.25 -300.39 26.67 l -300.39 42.88 b -300.39 45.42 -300.28 48.17 -300.05 51.13 -299.2 51.25 -297.67 51.31 -295.44 51.3 -289.55 51.31 -285.23 50.69 -282.52 49.45 l -282.11 49.45 -283.14 54.77 -307.2 54.77 m -264.2 43.22 b -265.78 42.66 -267.61 42.36 -269.66 42.36 -271.72 42.36 -273.2 42.69 -274.13 43.34 -274.7 44.23 -275 45.41 -275 46.89 -275 48.38 -274.59 49.53 -273.78 50.38 -272.98 51.23 -271.97 51.66 -270.75 51.66 -269.55 51.66 -268.31 51.33 -267.03 50.7 -265.77 50.06 -264.83 49.38 -264.2 48.66 l -264.2 43.22 m -263.28 51.53 b -265.63 54.11 -268.28 55.41 -271.22 55.41 -274.16 55.41 -276.47 54.77 -278.14 53.5 -279.81 52.23 -280.66 50.19 -280.66 47.36 -280.66 44.53 -279.66 42.5 -277.69 41.27 -275.7 40.03 -272.91 39.42 -269.28 39.42 l -264.2 39.59 -264.2 36.3 b -264.2 34.27 -264.7 32.61 -265.7 31.34 -266.7 30.08 -268.23 29.44 -270.27 29.44 -271.77 29.47 -274.17 30.92 -277.48 33.77 -278.59 32.34 -279.39 30.5 -279.84 28.22 -276.03 27 -272.53 26.38 -269.34 26.38 -266.16 26.38 -263.59 27.2 -261.67 28.86 -259.75 30.52 -258.78 32.86 -258.78 35.89 l -258.78 45.59 b -258.75 47.33 -258.47 48.94 -257.95 50.41 -257.42 51.89 -256.75 52.92 -255.91 53.5 l -255.78 54.08 -261.95 55.58 b -262.45 54.34 -262.91 53 -263.28 51.53 l -263.28 51.53 m -239.52 48.66 b -236.52 40.03 -234.63 34.17 -233.86 31.05 -234.63 29.25 -235.19 28.2 -235.53 27.94 l -235.53 27.23 -228.09 26.84 -228.09 27.53 b -228.09 28.64 -227.11 32.09 -225.14 37.86 l -221.39 48.94 b -218.86 41.13 -217.38 36.41 -216.95 34.75 -216.14 32.05 -215.73 29.72 -215.73 27.77 l -215.73 27.06 -210.09 27.06 -210.09 27.77 b -211.05 28.64 -211.97 30.52 -212.86 33.36 l -218.63 52.23 -219.38 55.28 -224.8 55.41 -225.78 52.11 -231.72 36.7 -236.92 52.23 -237.55 55.28 -243.03 55.41 -244.02 52.11 -251.58 33.13 b -252.66 30.33 -253.64 28.63 -254.52 28.05 l -254.52 27.36 -246.2 26.67 -246.2 27.36 b -246.2 28.7 -245.27 32.08 -243.38 37.45 l -239.52 48.66 m -198.14 54.77 l -205.58 54.77 -205.58 54.08 b -204.92 52.16 -204.59 49.11 -204.59 44.95 l -204.59 20.89 b -204.59 17.81 -205.48 15.44 -207.25 13.73 l -207.25 13.05 -199.34 11.66 -199 12.23 b -199.13 13.36 -199.17 17.05 -199.17 23.31 l -199.13 44.95 b -199.13 49.11 -198.8 52.16 -198.14 54.08 l -198.14 54.77 m -179.5 55.41 b -183.53 55.41 -186.69 54.16 -188.97 51.66 -191.23 49.16 -192.38 45.86 -192.38 41.75 -192.38 37.66 -191.09 34.08 -188.56 31 -186.02 27.92 -182.86 26.38 -179.09 26.38 -172.2 26.38 -168.77 30.63 -168.77 39.13 l -170.91 41.2 -186.25 41.2 b -186.25 44.44 -185.56 46.86 -184.17 48.48 -182.78 50.09 -180.92 50.91 -178.58 50.91 -177.66 50.91 -176.34 50.63 -174.66 50.06 -172.95 49.5 -171.45 48.84 -170.16 48.08 l -168.7 50.27 b -169.44 51 -171.03 52.03 -173.47 53.38 -175.91 54.73 -177.92 55.41 -179.5 55.41 l -179.5 55.41 m -180.14 29.27 b -181.75 29.27 -183 29.63 -183.89 30.36 -184.61 31.36 -185.19 32.63 -185.61 34.17 -186.03 35.7 -186.25 37.05 -186.25 38.2 l -174.42 37.75 b -174.42 32.09 -176.33 29.27 -180.14 29.27 l -180.14 29.27 m -157.09 30.02 b -157.8 30.7 -158.14 31.66 -158.14 32.88 -158.14 34.08 -157.75 35.03 -156.98 35.7 -156.22 36.38 -155.25 36.86 -154.08 37.17 -152.89 37.47 -151.64 37.86 -150.3 38.33 -148.94 38.78 -147.69 39.28 -146.52 39.8 -145.34 40.31 -144.36 41.16 -143.59 42.3 -142.83 43.45 -142.44 44.86 -142.44 46.52 -142.44 49.44 -143.52 51.66 -145.67 53.16 -147.83 54.66 -150.67 55.41 -154.19 55.41 -157.7 55.41 -160.83 54.5 -163.56 52.69 -163.45 50.73 -162.88 48.98 -161.83 47.44 -158.38 50.59 -155.22 52.17 -152.38 52.17 -151.14 52.17 -150.05 51.92 -149.08 51.42 -148.16 50.61 -147.69 49.53 -147.69 48.16 -147.69 46.8 -148.22 45.73 -149.28 44.98 -150.34 44.23 -151.63 43.66 -153.13 43.23 -154.63 42.8 -156.13 42.33 -157.63 41.78 -159.13 41.25 -160.39 40.41 -161.45 39.25 -162.52 38.09 -163.05 36.59 -163.05 34.75 -163.05 32.05 -162.03 29.98 -160.02 28.55 -158 27.09 -155.45 26.38 -152.38 26.38 -149.3 26.38 -146.27 27.03 -143.31 28.34 -143.66 30.03 -144.33 31.72 -145.33 33.42 -148.06 30.69 -150.91 29.33 -153.88 29.31 -155.14 29.33 -156.22 29.55 -157.09 30.02 l -157.09 30.02 m -130.66 30.02 b -131.36 30.7 -131.7 31.66 -131.7 32.88 -131.7 34.08 -131.31 35.03 -130.55 35.7 -129.78 36.38 -128.81 36.86 -127.64 37.17 -126.45 37.47 -125.2 37.86 -123.86 38.33 -122.5 38.78 -121.25 39.28 -120.08 39.8 -118.91 40.31 -117.92 41.16 -117.16 42.3 -116.39 43.45 -116 44.86 -116 46.52 -116 49.44 -117.08 51.66 -119.23 53.16 -121.39 54.66 -124.23 55.41 -127.75 55.41 -131.27 55.41 -134.39 54.5 -137.13 52.69 -137.02 50.73 -136.44 48.98 -135.39 47.44 -131.94 50.59 -128.78 52.17 -125.94 52.17 -124.7 52.17 -123.61 51.92 -122.64 51.42 -121.72 50.61 -121.25 49.53 -121.25 48.16 -121.25 46.8 -121.78 45.73 -122.84 44.98 -123.91 44.23 -125.19 43.66 -126.69 43.23 -128.19 42.8 -129.69 42.33 -131.19 41.78 -132.69 41.25 -133.95 40.41 -135.02 39.25 -136.08 38.09 -136.61 36.59 -136.61 34.75 -136.61 32.05 -135.59 29.98 -133.58 28.55 -131.56 27.09 -129.02 26.38 -125.94 26.38 -122.86 26.38 -119.83 27.03 -116.88 28.34 -117.22 30.03 -117.89 31.72 -118.89 33.42 -121.63 30.69 -124.47 29.33 -127.44 29.31 -128.7 29.33 -129.78 29.55 -130.66 30.02 l -130.66 30.02 m -91.19 33.13 b -91.19 38.67 -89.84 42.98 -87.17 46.05 -84.5 49.13 -81.19 50.67 -77.22 50.67 -74.33 50.67 -70.5 49.36 -65.73 46.75 l -64.17 49.11 b -65.95 50.42 -67.33 51.36 -68.3 51.94 -69.28 52.52 -70.39 53.11 -71.63 53.73 -74.13 54.92 -76.8 55.52 -79.64 55.52 -84.64 55.52 -88.91 53.66 -92.42 49.92 -95.94 46.19 -97.7 41.19 -97.7 34.92 -97.7 28.64 -95.67 23.55 -91.59 19.59 -87.52 15.66 -82.45 13.69 -76.41 13.69 -72.38 13.69 -68.58 14.61 -65.05 16.45 -65.5 18.88 -66.31 20.92 -67.47 22.56 -71.42 19.38 -75.72 17.78 -80.33 17.78 -81.72 17.78 -83.06 17.92 -84.38 18.19 -86.33 19.64 -87.95 21.63 -89.25 24.13 -90.53 26.63 -91.19 29.63 -91.19 33.13 l -91.19 33.13 m -56.97 46.75 l -56.97 35.55 b -56.97 32.13 -57.92 29.75 -59.84 28.39 l -59.84 27.7 -51.72 26.31 -51.38 26.89 b -51.48 28.02 -51.55 29.61 -51.55 31.69 l -51.55 45.3 b -51.55 49.16 -51.06 52.17 -50.09 54.36 l -50.09 54.77 -57.89 54.77 -57.89 54.36 b -57.27 52.56 -56.97 50.02 -56.97 46.75 l -56.97 46.75 m -52.13 13.91 b -51.58 14.38 -51.31 15.48 -51.31 17.27 -51.31 17.69 -51.33 18.06 -51.38 18.41 l -51.83 18.81 b -53.38 19.23 -55.2 19.55 -57.31 19.73 l -57.83 19.52 b -58.41 18.52 -58.7 17.19 -58.7 15.53 -58.7 15.34 -58.7 15.14 -58.7 14.95 l -58.23 14.55 b -56.39 13.94 -54.63 13.63 -52.92 13.63 -52.73 13.63 -52.47 13.72 -52.13 13.91 l -52.13 13.91 m -35.61 48.3 b -35.61 50.34 -35 51.36 -33.77 51.36 -32.72 51.36 -30.97 50.75 -28.52 49.52 l -27.3 51.53 b -28.53 52.38 -30.06 53.23 -31.92 54.11 -33.77 54.97 -35.45 55.41 -37 55.41 -38.53 55.41 -39.59 54.92 -40.17 53.95 -40.75 53 -41.03 51.61 -41.03 49.8 l -41.03 30.36 -46.23 30.64 -44.84 26.89 b -44.16 26.97 -42.92 27.05 -41.16 27.13 -41.22 25.2 -41.34 23.47 -41.5 21.94 l -35.61 20.44 -35.61 27.06 b -33.53 27 -30.7 26.77 -27.13 26.38 l -28.75 30.88 b -30.81 30.58 -33.11 30.38 -35.61 30.3 l -35.61 48.3 m -11.31 49.45 b -7.63 38.19 -5.77 31.5 -5.77 29.38 -5.77 28.72 -5.91 28.19 -6.17 27.77 l -6.17 27.06 0 27.06 0 27.77 b -0.58 28.27 -3.72 37.08 -9.41 54.19 -12.14 62.19 -13.7 66.97 -14.08 68.5 l -14.08 68.97 -21.23 69.48 -21.3 69.08 b -18.48 65.73 -16.03 61.23 -13.91 55.58 -14.14 54.92 -17.47 47 -23.89 31.8 -24.66 30 -25.48 28.72 -26.38 28 l -26.38 27.3 -18.64 26.67 -18.64 27.36 b -18.64 28.36 -18.17 30.3 -17.25 33.16 -16.33 36.03 -14.34 41.45 -11.31 49.45 l -11.31 49.45
The Lawless City
So, this is it.
Yeah.
The Crimson Tower, ruled by the Blood Queen.
One of the three rulers of the Lawless City.
A castle of vampires, eh?
And look, not even the
corpse-raiding vultures dare to go near it.
They think if they get too close, it's all over,
that they'll end up as hideous ghouls.
You scared or something?.
Don't be ridiculous!
It's just a hangout for a bunch of shut-ins.
With the power of Goldy Gilded—
You vermin aren't worthy
to pass through this gate.
The only ones permitted are servants
or guests of the Blood Queen, and powerful warriors.
I get it, and you're right.
We're neither servants nor guests.
But powerful warriors,
here to hunt the Blood Queen!
What's so funny?
I thought myself a fool,
which is why it's always so amusing
to find an even bigger fool than I am.
This is what happens to the likes of us
who dare challenge the Blood Queen!
I lost my right arm, and now I'm kept here
as a pathetic watchdog on a leash.
Well, we're no small fries like you!
Here's something to think about
in the afterlife!
My power level is 4,317.5!
I was just like you once.
They called me the White Devil.
The White Devil?!
The criminal with
the huge bounty on his head?!
But here, I'm nothing more than
a lowly gatekeeper!
Ripping apart idiots like you who don't know their place
is the only joy I have left in life!
Here he comes!
Right!
Yes, this place is just perfect!
The Lawless City is even more
of a dump than I imagined!
Stop gawking.
You don't wanna
catch the attention of any weirdos.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey...
What?
Aren't we going to that tower?
You are so...
First, I'm going to the Dark Knight Association
for a strategy meeting.
Dark Knight Association?
Never saw any of those back home.
That's because we have our own Knight Order.
The Dark Knight Association is an unofficial organization
founded for Dark Knights that don't belong to any public institution.
When a government
or landowner cannot cover...
The summer of my last year of high school...
I, Kageno Minoru, was following the road
to becoming the Eminence in Shadow,
Deceased ~ Kageno Minoru (18)
when my journey came to an abrupt end.
Or so it seemed.
But one thing led to another...
This stuff turned into that...
And that, I don't even know...
This, this, and that were all like this,
and it was kinda like this...
Then all this happened, and...
Here we are.
And that's it!
Imatry Nottaloos is down for the count!
And the winner is...
Claire Kagenou!
My sister won
the Bushin Festival championship.
To celebrate, I used my connections
with Gamma and got dressed up for a free...
Excuse me, I mean had a high-end,
fancy dinner at a Mitsugoshi restaurant, but...
I'm going to the Lawless City
to exterminate vampires.
Heading to battle as soon
as the tournament ended.
I know she's my sister,
but even I wonder
how hot-blooded she can be.
I brought you here with me
out of consideration for your future, you know.
My future?
If you stay behind me
and do everything I say,
I'll pry open a spot for you
in Midgar's Knight Order after you graduate.
Oh, okay.
Trying to bulk up my resumé
to make me a government employee?
Come to think of it, I haven't really considered
what I'll do after I graduate.
Claire'll inherit
the estate out in the boondocks,
so I think they'll stick me
in some kinda job somewhere.
As long as I can do what I wanna do,
I don't think I care whatever job I end up in.
And what is it that you "want to do"?
A secret.
I make it a point not to tell anyone
the things that really matter to me.
You're just making that up.
Stop trying to hide the fact
that you just haven't thought about it.
Why do you assume that?
Whatever, it's fine.
No, it's not.
It's not fine.
Hello there! Come take a look,
my beautiful young lady!
I just got a new stock of high-quality pets!
You're talking to me?
Yes, you!
The most beautiful young lady in the world!
You have a good eye.
He's buttering you up, Sis.
You be quiet!
But please, come look, miss!
These lucky finds just came in this morning!
This is today's hot item!
The pet Dark Knight, Little Goldy!
Whaddaya say?!
He's quite the handsome specimen,
a perfect fit for a lovely lady!
He's a total wreck.
Can't you at least handle
your products more carefully?
Well, I guess he did get
a little banged up in transit.
All right, he's worth 30 million zeni,
but I'll let you have him for 27.
He looks kinda familiar...
It's a little steep.
Okay, I get it.
Look, I'll throw in this guy
as a special deal!
Another fresh new catch, Cue Ball Quinton!
Well? Two pets
for the low price of 40 million!
You can't possibly say no to that!
He's been sliced through the middle.
Okay, okay! 37 million zeni!
Can't go any lower than that!
Not interested.
Wow, you drive a hard bargain!
I've seen him somewhere before...
All right, I'll let you
have 'em for 35 million!
I'm sorry...
but I have all the pets I need.
I see, so you prefer younger pups.
In that case, I think I'm expecting
a Dark Knight Academy student deep in debt...
Come on, we're walking.
I think it was Skull, or Skinny...
I can't walk when you're dragging me.
If I don't keep a hand on you,
you'll get lost.
No, I won't.
Yes, you will.
No, I will not.
I know for a fact you will.
I did.
I just came out for a minute
since I was bored at the inn.
Oops, my bad.
And that's what we call "karma".
Coming through.
Sorry about that, kid.
You need to be getting home, little boy.
Pleasure doing business!
It's always been a dog-eat-dog world,
but I can't believe I'm making bank
just by taking a stroll.
This city is heaven for me.
Now you've really done it, punk!
How're ya gonna make it up to us, huh?!
I'm in a bad enough mood already!
I lost my bet, my dear sweet Marie
turned me down,
and it's all your fault!
You rotten little—
So, that's a ghoul. A vampire underling.
I've heard they have, like, tons of HP,
but I guess 'round here,
they're just everyone's punching bag.
It really is a dog-eat-dog world.
Just what I'd expect from
a town drenched in blood and slaughter.
A wave of magical energy?
H-Hey!
This thing was still alive?!
A human turns into a ghoul
when bitten by one.
Apparently, that was only
a rumor, when actually...
Oh, is that why?
The red moon is stimulating
all the magical energy in town.
If I don't do anything,
they'll just keep multiplying.
What to do?
Run away like
a background character, as usual?
Or go for a "mysterious young man" act
since what happens in the Lawless City stays in the Lawless City?
Anyway, since I do get to be
in a zombie apocalypse,
I think I'll let things get
a little bit more out of hand before I...
Get down!
You are?
I am Mary.
The Ancient Vampire Hunter.
"Ancient"?
Run, if you value your life.
"Run... if you value your life."
The frenzy has begun.
"The frenzy... has begun!"
The moon is red.
We are out of time.
"We are... out of time."
What is happening?
What is this feeling?
This thrill in my heart?
Yes...
This is...
Did he not hear me?
I told him to be a good boy
and wait at the inn.
I-I'm saved—
Hey, you.
Have you seen a boy
with black hair and black eyes?
N-No, I haven't!
Oh.
Where did that idiot wander off to?
O-O-Our time has come, Po!
Indeed!
Th-Th-The academy will never find us here!
They can't possibly expel us!
It was s-s-so worth risking
our lives to come here!
Our summer may be over...
...but our virginity is still
going strong, my dear Skel!
You got that right!
When will we ever become real adults?!
Now, of course!
Into the splendor...
...of the world of maturity!
Let's go—
What was that for?!
You are way too excited!
That dirty old bastard...
How long will this go on?
What now? Another street fight?
I'm trying to wallow in misery here.
Who's there?
I'm not taking any more customers tonight...
Run, if you value your life.
The frenzy has begun.
Frenzy?
The moon is red.
We are out of time.
W-Wait!
Wh-Who are you?
Shadow.
Run, if you value your life.
The frenzy has begun.
The moon is red.
We are out of time.
Marie! Marie, are you okay?
There are ghouls outside, and—
What happened in here?
Well, a man named Shadow...
Shadow?
You mean the Shadow?
You've heard of him?
He's the evil mastermind who had
a field day beating up the corrupt clergy!
He's at least as dangerous as
any of the rulers of this city!
But he...
He didn't seem like a bad man.
What are you doing, Marie?
I'm getting out of this crazy,
messed-up town.
By breaking your contract??
But who knows what they'll do
if they find you!
Thank you, Shadow.
Try to escape, if you so desire.
If you are fortunate,
you may even be successful in your attempt.
Of course, the past is never so kind
as to let anyone go.
Lady Yukime!
The vampires have set ghouls loose in the city!
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry, Cid.
If only I hadn't brought you
to this horrible place...
Are you the woman who's been going around
asking about a boy with black hair and black eyes?
Because I met one not long ago.
I've already found him.
He's my brother, but I've found him now.
That boy doesn't have
black hair or black eyes.
What?
Then who the hell are you?
I met two men who matched the description.
Tell me!
I saw the first one when the moon
was beginning to turn red,
standing in front
of a rampaging ghoul and smiling.
That can't be him. My brother may scream,
but he would never smile.
I saw the second one
a couple of minutes ago.
A young Dark Knight
with no noticeable features.
Where was he? Tell me!
He was about to be taken away
by the followers of the Blood Queen.
The Blood...
Where did they take him?
The Crimson Tower?
Your brother is in the Crimson Tower,
the Blood Queen's castle.
The vampires wish to offer him
as a sacrifice to the Blood Queen.
Sacrifice?
To awaken Blood Queen Elisabeth
from her thousand-year slumber,
they require the blood
of a living young man.
Wait.
I've never heard about
the Blood Queen being asleep.
They've kept that fact secret,
biding their time.
Waiting a millennium for the night
that would give the vampires tremendous power...
The night the Red Moon would rise again.
It's true, the moon has seemed redder
these last few days.
The Red Moon affects
the sleeping queen, as well.
With the sacrifice's blood
as a catalyst, she will surely...
But what you're saying
is Cid's in the tower, right?
That he's still alive because they need
the blood of the living.
My target is the Blood Queen Elisabeth.
To find her, I must go to the Crimson Tower.
Then we're heading in the same direction.
Let's work together, Miss...
Mary.
I am a vampire hunter.
The name's Claire.
It will be difficult to get in
from the ground floor, but I know a way.
Follow me.
Got it!
I'm coming for you, Cid!
We're dead! We're gonna die as virgins!
You gotta be kidding!
Other than my mom,
I've never even kissed a—
Skel, my friend!
I'll never forget your virginity!
Hey, wait up! Don't just leave me here!
Boobies!
J-Juggernaut, sir?
Don't you just love that smell?
Like a nice, big fight is brewing.
Haven't seen one like this
since the therianthrope invasion way back when.
Now's our chance! Retreat!
Run across the rooftops to the station!
What do you think you're doing?
And you call yourself Association Knights?
I don't give a damn
about your association's honor!
They don't pay us enough for this!
Forget it!
Ugh, those lousy scavengers...
Director, we can't hold
the main street any longer!
They're already here?!
Run, if you value your life.
The frenzy has begun.
Who are you?
H-He's the wanted criminal!
The moon is red.
We are out of time.
We have little time remaining.
Lord Crimson.
Preparations for the sacrifice
are almost complete.
And our takeover of the city
is going as planned, however...
However?
We're meeting unexpected resistance
in certain locations.
We know who's behind that.
The fools who babble on
with their nonsensical idea of being my equal.
Yukime the Spirit Fox,
ruler of the White Tower,
and Juggernaut the Tyrant,
ruler of the Black Tower.
But let them play their games.
They will meet their end as soon
as the Blood Queen revives.
Yes, Lord, but there is one other.
What?
There is someone going around
the city killing ghouls.
Stay out of this, gruntlings!
Go to Hell, she-fox!
You truly are a thorn in my side.
I insist you cease opening your mouth
and spewing your rancid breath across the city.
You're the one who reeks, animal lady!
Such a bothersome pest!
Nothing changes.
Someone, somewhere,
may be trying to spin a new tale.
But I do not change.
I only continue on my quest
to become the Eminence in Shadow!
Who are you?
You're...
I am Shadow.
He who lurks in the shadows
in order to hunt the shadows.
that
is
too
late
That
is
too
late
Can't
catch
up
with
a
move
like
that
is
to
say
That
ture
The
first
move
sets
the
unknown
future
this
way
It's
just
last
move
will
dictate
the
world's
answer
it's
me
That
I
alone
am
the
victor
This
gaze
fixed
on
a
turn
winning
move
with
no
one
the
wiser
game
Total
domination
is
the
name
of
the
game
battle
of
wits
mis
take
Even
mistakes
are
calculated
play
check
mate
Sacrifices
made
to
achieve
checkmate
king
game
A
fight
to
claim
each
other's
king
Where
ideologies
and
desires
are
tested
one chance minogasanu akushu
One chance, no flaw will escape my gaze
last chance kanarazu shitomeru
Last chance to end this power game
that is too late
That is too late
sonna te ja mou oitsukenai
Can't catch up with a move like that
that is to say
That is to say
kanzen shouri wa kono te no naka ni
Total victory lies in the palm of my hand
catch
up
to
me
now